cryptomundo.com 2019-05-03

# Cryptomundo » Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers all of the Cryptomundo LLC (“Cryptomundo”) domains, subdomains, and the servers and networks which power them (“Cryptomundo Site”) and all content, which may be updated by Cryptomundo from time to time. Cryptomundo will provide notice of any change to the Privacy Policy [here](https://cryptomundo.com//privacy-policy/ "Cryptomundo Privacy Policy").

Please read this statement carefully before accessing the Cryptomundo Site. Your access to the Cryptomundo Site indicates your agreement to abide by the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not access or use the Cryptomundo Site.

**Information Collection**

Cryptomundo is the sole owner of the information collected and displayed on the Cryptomundo Site. Cryptomundo may collect information from our users at several different points on the Cryptomundo Site.

**Comments**

In order to enhance their use of the Cryptomundo Site, users can choose to post comments on particular articles of interest. To leave a comment, users must submit certain personal information, including a valid email address. Cryptomundo uses this information to screen users who leave comments in violation of our Terms and will not disclose any readily identifiable personal information to any other organization.

**Mailing List**

Cryptomundo may launch a mailing list for some or all of the Cryptomundo Site. To sign up to receive regular emails from the Cryptomundo Site mailing list, users must submit personal information, including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information may be used in aggregate form only to assess general user interests in products and services. Users who subscribe to a mailing list will receive regular emails from the Cryptomundo Site, including new articles and emails from third party sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from sponsors, do not sign up for the mailing list.

**Discussion Group and Cookies**

Cryptomundo may launch a discussion board service on some or all of the Cryptomundo Site where users can discuss common topics of interest. Users will have the option of signing up for this service, and to do so must submit certain personal information, including a valid email address. Cryptomundo uses this information to screen users who leave comments in violation of our Terms and will not disclose any readily identifiable personal information to any other organization.

The discussion board service may use cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

By accepting a cookie from the Cryptomundo Site, users will not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on the site’s discussion board. We store a cookie on each user’s machine that contains a username and encrypted password. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to use Cryptomundo products or services that require you to sign in, and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings.

**Links**

The Cryptomundo Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Cryptomundo is not responsible for the privacy and content policies of other sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected at the Cryptomundo Site. Please use care in accessing other web sites.

**Third Party Cookies**

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). Cryptomundo has no control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers use of cookies by Cryptomundo only and not the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered by third party providers such as Google®. Information about visits to this site, such as number of visits (but not username or any personal information), is used to select and display ads to users on this Cryptomundo Site.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files, including internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track aggregate movements of users, and gather demographic information. This information is not associated to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Cryptomundo may need to disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. Cryptomundo also may disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Terms and Privacy Policy, to respond to claims of violation of third party rights, and to protect property and personal safety.

**Business Transitions**

In the event Cryptomundo goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or part of its assets, any or all Cryptomundo data may be transferred to a third party.

**International Users**

By visiting our web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of the Cryptomundo Site, we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, please understand that such data may be stored on servers located in or outside of the United States. By providing us with your data, you consent to the use and transfer of such data.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact the editor of the Cryptomundo Site in question, or send an email to us using the [contact form](https://cryptomundo.com//contact-us/ "Cryptomundo Contact Form").

Privacy Policy Amendments

**UPDATED PRIVACY POLICY-03/02/2018**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Cryptomundo.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://cryptomundo.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Cryptomundo.com.  
**  
Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Cryptomundo.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  
• To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
• To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
• To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
• To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.  
• To send periodic emails

We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.  
**  
Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensor and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.  
****

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>  
**  
Changes to this privacy policy**

Cryptomundo.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.  
**  
Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us [here](https://cryptomundo.com//contact-us/ "Cryptomundo Contact Form").
